Guide to the Open University Records
University of Houston Libraries
Open University Records
1970-1979
09/1969-076
Open University Records, 1970-1979
19.00 linear feet
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
These records are contained in 18 record cartons. The materials relate to the Open University program and include correspondence, reports, program information, workbooks and classroom supplements.
Biographical Information -
In 1969, The University of Houston was one of four universities in the United States to utilize this new concept in education. The purpose of the “Open University” program was to provide better university education for large groups of students through successful self-study programs which covered the relationships between the sciences and society and the arts and society. Through the use of a wide range of multi-media material, including closed circuit television and radio programs and self-study texts, students were able to learn on their own without being required to spend numerous hours in the classroom.
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name -
University of Houston
Genre/Form of Material -
Correspondence; Publications (document genre); Videocassettes
Topical Term -
British Open University; Distance education; Education; Open learning; Southern Association of Schools and Colleges; Television in higher education; University extension
Conditions Governing Access -
Open for research.
Acquisition Information
Information of acquisition method not available.
Scope and Contents
These records are contained in 18 record cartons. The materials relate to the Open University program and include correspondence, reports, program information, workbooks and classroom supplements. The collection is organized in 3 series; Administrative Files, Classroom Materials, Audio/Video Tapes. Each series is arranged alphabetically by subject title. Materials range in year from 1970 to 1979.
Detailed List of Contents
- Administrative Files, 1970-1979
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes 4 boxes of administrative material, ranging from 1970 to 1979. It includes articles, correspondence, budget and finance material, and grade sheets. This series includes reference material from the British Open University Program.
  - Open University Program Articles and Papers (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - Open University Article Pamphlets Naomi E. McIntosh (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Accreditation of OPU Courses (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Admission to OPU-COL (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Advanced Placement Tests Change of Major Forms (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Advertising-OPU (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Book Orders (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Book Orders, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Book Orders - OPU COL (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - British Open University Conference (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - British Open University General (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - British Open University Visitors (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Broadcast Rights and Fees - British OPU (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Budget Activity Report - K-0503, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Budget Activity Report - L-0103, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Budget Grant Conditions AandS-M-01 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Budget Material (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Budget Material, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Budget Material 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Cable TV Project (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Center for Open Learning (originals for copying) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Class Schedules - OPU and COL (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - COL - Course Directors notices to (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - COL - Description of (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - COL - Grade Distribution (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - COL - Transition Form OPU (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - College of Social Science (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - College of Technology (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Colson, Anthony C. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Complaints (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Computer (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Conferences/Consortiums/Coup, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Coordinating Board (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Copyright Law, January 1, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Course - Age of Revolutions (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Course - Anyone for Tennyson? (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Course - Art America (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Course - Business Management (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Course - Catalog Revision (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Course - Cinematic Eye, Spring 1979 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Course - Costs (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Course - Death and Dying (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Course - Descriptions (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Course - Eng 130, Spring 1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Course - General (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Course - Human Development (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Course - Humanities in Drama (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Course - Humanities/ Fine Arts (Final Exam) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Course - Japan HIS 387B, Spring 1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Course - Long Search (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Course - Manmade World (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Course - Mathematics Found (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Course - Mathematics Special 131 Younglove (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Course - Mathematics 231 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Course - Molding of America Society/Values (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Course Guide - MTH 231and 232 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Course - Newspaper Courses (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Course - Off-Campus Courses (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Course - Pharmacy Course (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Course - Psychology 133(tapes) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Course - Psychology 133 HISD (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Course - Romantic Rebellion (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Course - Roots (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Course - Science Foundation (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Course - Science and Rise of Technology (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Course - Shakespeare Plays, Spring 1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Course - Social Science Foundation (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Course Guide - Urban Development (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Course - Urban Development (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Course - Urban Development 1 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Course - Urban Development Original, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Course - Urban Development DT201 27-29 Supplementary material 19-22 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Course - Third Testament (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Course - Woman and the Law (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Course Calendars - Originals (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Course Descriptions - Originals (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Course Handouts, Fall 1976 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Course Handouts, Spring 1977 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Course Handouts, Summer 1977 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Course Handouts, Fall 1977 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Course Handouts, Spring 1978 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Credit for Non-College Learning (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Open University-delivery of films and open materials, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Distance Registration, Summer 1979 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - English Credit (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - English Proficiency Requirement, July 1977 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Evaluation of OU by ETS CEEB (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Examination, Credit by (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Open University Program Fact Sheets (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Film and Import Information (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Formal Science Credit Forms (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Open University General Information and Correspondence, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Grade Sheets, Fall 1972 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Grade Sheets, Spring 1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Grade Sheets, Fall 1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Grade Sheets, Spring 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Grade Sheets, Fall 1974 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Grade Sheets, Spring 1975 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Grade Sheets, Fall 1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Grade Sheets, Spring 1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Grade Sheets, Summer 1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Grade Sheets, Fall 1976 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Grade Sheets, Fall 1977 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Grade Sheets, Spring 1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Grades, Spring 1978 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Grades, Spring 1979 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Grant Information (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Handicapped Person in the Community (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Health Service Fee Waiver (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Humanities Handout (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - IDT’s, Summer - Fall 1974 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - IDT’s, Fall 1975 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - IDT’s, Spring - Summer 1975 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - IDT’s, 1976 - 1977 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - IDT’s COL K 0503, 1977 - 1978 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Incompletes (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Klein Project (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - KUHT TV (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Letters to Students General Meeting (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Long Distance Registration (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Mexico Open University (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Mission Self-Study (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - NSF Proposal (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Open University (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Open University (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - PAR’s, Spring 1975 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Personnel Information (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Open University Program Pamphlets (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Open University Program Pamphlets (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Open University Program Pamphlets (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Progress Report - OPU, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Progress Report - OPU, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Purchase Req. Vouchers etc., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Purchase Orders and Receiving Reports (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Purchase Requisitions (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Purchase Requisitions, 1976 - 1977 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Purchase Requisitions/ Vouchers COL K 0503, 1977 - 1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Purchase Vouchers, 1976 - 1977 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Purchase Vouchers, Bills, etc. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Purchase Vouchers (Falls) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Relations with other Pilot Program Institution (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Report to Fields, letter to Hoffman (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - The Open University - re Television (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Open University- Reviews and Evaluations of Materials (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Roll (State Audit), Fall 1972 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Roll (State Audit), Spring 1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Roll (State Audit), Fall 1973 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Roll (State Audit), Spring 1974 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Roll (State Audit), Fall 1974 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Roll (State Audit), Spring 1975 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Roll (State Audit), Fall 1975 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Roll (State Audit), Spring 1976 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Roll (State Audit), Summer 1976 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Roll (State Audit), Fall 1976 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Roll (State Audit), Spring 1977 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Roll (State Audit), Summer 1977 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Roll (State Audit), Fall 1977 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Roll (State Audit), Spring 1978 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Roll (State Audit), Fall 1978 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Sesame Newspaper, September - October 1977 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Southern Association of Schools and Colleges (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Special Students General (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Special Students, Fall 1976 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Special Students, Fall 1977 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Special Students, Spring 1977 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Special Students, Summer 1977 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Special Students, Spring 1978 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Special Students, Fall 1978 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Special Students Approved by Admissions, Spring 1979 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Special Students Approved, (application forwarded to Adm.), Summer 1979 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Special Studies, Fall 1974 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Staff Reclassification (Old) (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Student Services- U of H (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - KK, Summer 1979 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Open University Type Courses (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Classroom Material
  This series includes 9 record cartons of classroom materials arranged by one of the following subject titles; Art, Education, Math, Science and Technology. Course guides, teacher’s guides, and textbooks will be found. The bulk of this series is classroom workbooks, also called unit books.
  - A1 Course Guide (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Arts A100 Course Unit Report for Analysis (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Arts A201 Post- Foundation Tuition, A Guide to the Course (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Arts A201 Units 1-6 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Arts A201 Units 7-16 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Arts A201 Units 17-23 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Arts A201 Units 24-32 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Arts A202 Course Guide (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Arts A202 Study Guide, Units 1-6 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Arts A202 Units 7-12 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Arts A202 Units 13-24 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Arts A202 Units 25-32 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Arts A301 Units 1-4 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Arts A302 Unit 31 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Arts A303 Units 1-8 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Arts A303 Units 9-15 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Arts A303 Units 19-25 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Arts A303 Units 28-32 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Arts A307 Description of Course, Book listing, A new Course, Theatres and staying (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Arts A307 Units 6 and 7 Study 4 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Arts A307 Units 14-15 Study 7, Isben’s, Checkov (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Arts A307 Shaw and Brecht, A Study in Six Parts (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Arts A307 The Director and The Stage, Study’s Memo, Intro. Note (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Arts A351 Mailing No. 1-5, Units 15 and 16 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Arts/Science/Math/Technology AMST 283 Getting Underway, Units 1-8 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Arts/Science/Math/Technology AMST 283 Units 9-16 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Arts/Science/Tech AST 281 A Guide to the Course (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Arts/Science/Technology AST 281 Post-Foundation Tuition Supplement (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Arts/Science/Technology AST 281 Units 1-7 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Arts/Science/Technology AST Units 8-13 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Arts/Science/Technology AST 281 Units 14-15 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Consumer Experience Proposal to Offer (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Consumer Experience Correspondence, Misc., Program Content Summary, Consumer Survival Kit (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Consumer Experiences Faculty Program Manual, Mid-Term Final Exams (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Consumer Experience Student Learning Guide (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Educational E201 Mailing No. 1-8 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Educational E201 Learner Project, Test Booklet-Study of Values, Sample Questionnaire (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Educational E201 Summary of Selected Research Reports, Using the Literature, Case-Study Option Manual (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Educational E201 Intro and Guide to Course, Methodology Handbook (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Educational E201 Block 1-3 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Educational E201 Block 5 and 6 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Educational E201 Supplementary/Folder Material (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Educational E201 Supplementary/Folder Material Block 1-8 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Educational E262 Supplementary Material Block 1-10, Cassette Notes (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Educational E262 Guide to Course, Block 1, Block 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Educational E262 Block 3-5 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Educational E262 Block 6-8 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Educational E351 Folder 1 Maps, Folder 2 Urban Childhood (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Educational E351 Block 1, Block 2 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Educational E351 Block 3, Block 4 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Educational E351 Block 5, Block 6 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Math M100 Course Guide (2), Course Description (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Math M100 Units 2, 9, 19-26 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Math M100 Units 27-34, User’s Guide (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Math M100 Commentaries on TV Components of Units 1-9, 10-18 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Math M100 Sections 1-13 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Math M100 Sections 14-36 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Math M100 Books Units 1-3 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Math M100 Books Unit 4-7 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Math M100 Books Unit 8-11 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Math M100 Books Units 12-14 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Math M100 Books Units 15-17 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Math M100 Books Units 18-20 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Math M100 Books Units 21-23 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Math M100 Books Units 24-27 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Math M100 Books Units 28-31 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Math M100 Books Units 33-36 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Math M202 Units 7-8 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Math M251 Data Structures (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Math 371-372 Getting Underway, Intro to Statistics (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Math/ Social Sciences/Technology MDT 241 Units 1-9 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Math/ Social Sciences/Technology MDT 241 Units 10-16 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Math/Science/ Tech. MST 281 Foundation Course Books, Course Outline, Course Description (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Math/Science/Tech. MST 281 Original Calculus IandII “Supplement” Course Guide (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Math/Science/Tech. MST 281 Supplementary Material Units 1-13 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Math/Science/Tech. MST 281 Supplementary Material Units 14-17 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Math/Science/Tech. MST 281 Units 1-8 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Math/Science/Tech. MST 281 Units 10-17 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Social Sciences D101 Units 11-14, Research opp., Books (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Social Sciences D231 Units 1-4, Units 9-12, Units 13-16 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Social Science D283 Unit 1-4 The Sociological Perspective, Social Interaction, Stratification and Social Class, Beliefs and Religion (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Social Sciences D283 Units 15-17 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Social Sciences D305 Supplementary Material 3 Block 4 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Social Sciences DT305 Block 12, Block 13, Block 14 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Social Sciences DT201 Units 1-29, Course Guide (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Social Sciences DT201 Units 1-9 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Social Sciences DT201 Units 10-14, 23-25 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Social Sciences DT201 Units 26-33 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Social Sciences DT201 Audio-Visual Handbooks 1-4 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Post Experience P853 Teacher’s Guide to drugs, Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Post Experience P853 Intro. and Guide, Using the Literature, Supplementary Material Block 1-3 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Post Experience P853 Guide to Case Files, Block 2 Case Files, Block 3 Case Files, case Files 6 and 7 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Post Experience P853 Units 1-4 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Post Experience P853 Units 5-8 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Post Experience P853 Units 9-13 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Post Experience P853 Units 14-16 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Post Experience PD251 Using the literature (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Educational Studies PE261 Unit 1-4 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - PE261 Unit 5-6 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Reading Curriculum Unit 10-17 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - PE 261 Reading Development, for Learning Activities, Broadcast notes, Using Literature (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Post Experience PET271 Block 2 Unit 4 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Technology/ Post Exp. PT272 Units 1-4 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Technology/ Post Exp. PT272 Units 5-8 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Science S2-2 Principles of Geochemistry Unit 1-6 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Science S23 Geology (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Science S24 Intro. and Guide to Course (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Science S25 Intro. and Guide to Course (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - S26- Science Earth Science Resources Block 4-6 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - S26- Science Earth Science Resources Block 1-4 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Science S100 Course Unit Report form Analysis (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Science S100 Summer School (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Science S100 Course Description, Course outline, Study Guide Units 1-34, Intro. andGuide to Course (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Science S100 The Chemical Balance (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Science S100 Broadcast Notes, Units 1-34 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Science S100 Math for Science, Guide to Math, Units 1and2 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Science S100 Units 3-7 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Science S100 Units 8-12 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Science S100 Units 13-16 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Science S100 Units 17-20 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Science S100 Units 21-23 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Science S100 Units 24-27 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Science S100 Units 28-30 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Science S100 Units 31-34 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Technology T100 The Man-made World (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Technology T241 Units 1-6 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Technology T241 Units 7-12 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Technology T241 Units 13-16 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Technology T242 Study Guide, Units 1-6 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Technology T242 Units 1-5 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Technology T242 Units 6-10 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Technology T242 Mailing No. 2-6 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Technology T242 Press Cutting Exercise, Role Playing, Activity Book (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Technology T242 Units 12-14 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Technology T242 Intray Analysis File 1-3 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Technology T242 Retailer- Agent Distributor Game (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Technology T262 Even Further Reading, Mailing No. 1-8 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Technology T262 Broadcast Notes, Computer- Marked Assignments, Tutor- Marked assignments (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Technology T262 Broadcast notes, Course Guide, Project Sampler (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Technology T262 Units 1,2-3, 6 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Technology T262 Units 9,12, 13-16 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - TAD292 Art and Environment Unit 0-2, 7-8 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Art and Environment Unit 3-6 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Art and Environment Unit 10-13 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Art and Environment Unit 14-16 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Art and Environment Supplementary notes Unit 6-8 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - TAD292 Student-tutor notes Unit 1-9 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - TAD292 NI-3 Student-tutor notes Unit 1-9 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - TAD292 Art and Environment Radio 1-4, 6-8, 9, 11 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - TAD292 Radio (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - TAD292 Art and Development TV 1-6 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - TAD292 TV 1-6 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - TM281 Math and Engineer Course (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - TS251 Review and revision (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Broadcast and Assignment Calendar, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Career Info. For Scottish Students (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Course Textbooks Catalogue, Book Catalogue Supplement, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - How to Study, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Misc. Papers (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - “New from Open University” A322, DE353, A307, D204, M341, PE231, S304, S322, TM281, E202, ED322 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Oceans Press Kit (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Open Line, Connection, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Open University Program Booklet (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Open University Program Supplements Age of Revolution and Romanticism (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Open University Program Supplements Humanities and Fine Arts (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Open University Program Supplements Math for Sciences, Technology Cal IandII (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Open University Program Supplements Science and Belief (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Open University Program Supplements Science and the Rise of Technology (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Sesame-Newspaper for Open University, September-October 1977 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Student Computing Service User’s Guide (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Students of the Open University - Their Background and Progress, 1972, Analysis of Student Progress 1974 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - The Adams Chronicle (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Teaching at a Distance Number 3 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Teaching Practical Physics (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Universities in Britain (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - An Introduction to Calculus and Algebra Vol. 1 Background to Calculus (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - An Introduction to Calculus and Algebra Vol. 2 Calculus Applied (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Europe 1780-1830, A General History of Europe, Franklin L. Ford (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Instructor’s manual General Statistics Second Edition (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Population Dynamics, Maurice E. Solomon (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Race Community and Conflict, John Rex and Robert Moore (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Readings in Urban Sociology, Edited by R.E. Pahl (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Report of the Vice-Chancellor, 1969 - 1970 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Report of the Vice-Chancellor, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Science and Religious Belief 1600-1900, Edited by D.C. Goodman (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - SK Science Kit Inc. (Box 13, Folder 11)